myshn.net 2015-09-20

# Privacy Policy | Skyhigh Networks

##### Last Updated: February 15, 2015

Skyhigh Networks, Inc. (“Skyhigh Networks” or “We”) values its customers and respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy discloses Skyhigh Networks’ information gathering and dissemination practices for the information collected through our call centers and websites operated by or on behalf of Skyhigh Networks, including without limitation, the website located at [www.skyhighnetworks.com](http://www.skyhighnetworks.com/) (such website shall hereinafter be referred to as this “Site”) and our service (Skyhigh Discovery and Risk Assessment) The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged Skyhigh Networks. We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy before using this Site. Your use of this Site signifies that you agree with all of the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, so please do not use this Site if you disagree with any part of this Privacy Policy. Our privacy commitment extends to Skyhigh Networks and all of our brands (which include, but are not limited to, Skyhigh Networks, and Skyhigh Cloud Discovery and Risk Assessment Service.)

Skyhigh Networks has been awarded TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with TRUSTe’s [Program Requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, [www.skyhighnetworks.com](http://www.skyhighnetworks.com/) and does not cover information that may be collected behind the login on our website. TRUSTe’s mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [privacy_policy@skyhighnetworks.com](mailto:privacy_policy@skyhighnetworks.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request).

Skyhigh Networks complies with the U.S. – E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S. – Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Skyhigh Networks has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Skyhigh Networks’ certification, please visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/

1\. **What are Skyhigh Networks’ practices regarding the collection and use of information?**

  1. Personally Identifiable Information: 
    1. We may collect personally identifiable information from you (including, without limitation, your nameemail address, phone number, event type and date) when you provide it to us such as when you create an account, enter a promotion, sign-up for a newsletter, participate in a survey, contact customer service or otherwise interact with us. We may maintain a record of the purchases you make with us.
    2. Personally identifiable information also includes information regarding which software-as-a-service (SaaS) websites, and any websites, are used, by whom used, when used and the frequency of use.
    3. We may use your personally identifiable information in the following ways:

      * To communicate with you and to send your information by email, postal mail, telephone, or other means about our products, services, promotions and the like;
      * To administer and fulfill information requests and our promotions and offers, and, if you order products or services, to process and fulfill your order and to send you emails to confirm your order status and shipment;
      * To help us learn more about your preferences;
      * To help us address problems with and improve our site design, products and services;
      * To enhance your experience with Skyhigh Networks;
      * To analyze trends and statistics;
      * To protect the security or integrity of our websites and business;
      * To contact you if necessary.

**Tracking Technologies**

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Skyhigh Networks, and our partners [e.g. analytics tools, marketing automation applications, ad retargeting services] ,affiliates, or analytics or service providers [customer support provider etc.]These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies to remember user form fill information such as name and email and to track users on our site and across the internet to deliver targeted advertising _._ Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.

We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 to store [content information and preferences.] Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as Flash to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash LSOs please click here:

<http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

Widgets: Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**What are Skyhigh Networks’ practices regarding sharing and disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information?**

  1. Provided that any such disclosure shall be aggregated and on an anonymous, non-personally identifiable basis, the Customer agrees that Skyhigh Networks may use for its business purposes portions of the Customer Data, or specific metrics derived from Customer’s usage of the Skyhigh Networks Services, or both.
  2. We may collect and aggregate statistics on our product usage and any related cloud service usage across Customers that will help Skyhigh Networks perform industry benchmarking of service usage, product usage trending, and for projecting business and operational scaling.
  3. We will share your personally identifiable information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy.We do not sell your personal information to third parties.
  4. We may provide your information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your information only as necessary to provide these services to us.
  5. If and when Skyhigh Networks is compelled to disclose information, personally identifiable information of any user may be shared with other companies outside Skyhigh Networks: (i) as permitted by law; (ii) in the event of a transfer of ownership or assets of Skyhigh Networks you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information;; (iii) in the event of a bankruptcy of Skyhigh Networks; (iv) where we determine that disclosure of specific information is necessary to comply with the request of a law enforcement or regulatory agency or other legal process; or (v) to protect the interests or safety of Skyhigh Networks or other visitors to this Site.

**How do I access or change my information?**

  1. You can review and change certain personally identifiable information related to your use of this Site (such as your name and contact information). To access your information at this Site, simply sign in to your account using your email address and password, and you will be able to edit or delete your personally identifiable information in your account profile. Login information, which is a basis for accessing our system is not immediately purged or deleted.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

  1. You can also ask us to update your personally identifiable information by contacting us as described in the section below entitled, “How do I contact you?” We will respond to your request to access within 30 days. Any request to update or delete your personal information may take up to 10 days for your email request and up to 8 weeks for your postal mail request. Requests should be emailed to [privacy_policy@skyhighnetworks.com](mailto:privacy_policy@skyhighnetworks.com).
  2. Customer Testimonials/Comments/Reviews: We post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer’s consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. To request removal of your personal information from Testimonials or comments please contact us at [privacy_policy@skyhighnetworks.com](mailto:privacy_policy@skyhighnetworks.com)

**How do I stop receiving Skyhigh Networks marketing communications?**

  1. If you prefer not to receive promotional emails, such as information about new products, special offers and sales events, from one or more of the Skyhigh Networks brands, you can let us know by contacting our customer service as described in the below section entitled, “How do I contact you?”. Please be sure to include your full name and the email address you used when you registered with or made a purchase from the Skyhigh Networks brand. It may take up to 10 days to process your email request.
  2. Please note that when you make an online purchase from us, we will continue to confirm your order status and shipment by email. We may also need to contact you via telephone, email or postal mail with questions or information regarding your order.

**Does Skyhigh Networks combine information from different sources?**

We may combine the personally identifiable information that we collect from you with other information about you that we collect or receive from other sources. This information may be used to improve our websites, to personalize your online experience, to tailor our communications with you, to determine the effectiveness of our advertising, and for other internal business purposes.

**How do I know my personally identifiable information is secure?**

  1. We have in place certain physical, electronic, contractual, and managerial safeguards to protect the security and privacy of your personally identifiable information. No company can fully eliminate security risks connected to handling information on the Internet. You should know that unauthorized persons might attempt to intercept your network communications. We encourage you to exercise caution in accessing Wi-Fi hotspots and other communications networks.
  2. When you enter your personally identifiable information on our websites, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect your information as it is transmitted to us. To make sure you are accessing our secure server before you submit personally identifiable financial information, look at your browser’s security level indicator to the right of the address bar or lower right corner of the window. If you see a solid key or a closed lock (depending upon your browser), then SSL is active. To double-check for security, look at the URL or Location line of your browser. If you have accessed a secure server, the first characters of the address in that line should change from “http” to “https.”

**What about links to other websites?**

For your convenience and information, this Site may contain links to other websites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the content or practices of any linked website. Please be aware that the terms of our Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites – we recommend that you review the privacy policy of any website that you access through this Site.

**How do I contact you?**

For questions about this Privacy Policy, to make choices about receiving promotional communications, to update your personally identifiable information, or to place an order, you can contact any of our Skyhigh Networks brands by email, telephone, or postal mail as follows: Skyhigh Networks, Inc. Attn: Customer Service 1601 S DeAnza Blvd, Suite 248, Cupertino, CA 95014 408-564-0278 privacy_policy@skyhighnetworks.com

**What law governs this Privacy Policy?**

This Site is controlled and operated by Skyhigh Networks from the United States, and is not intended to subject Skyhigh Networks or any Affiliated Entity to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, country or territory other than that of the United States. Skyhigh Networks does not represent or warrant that this Site, or any part thereof, is appropriate or available for use in any particular jurisdiction. Those who choose to access this Site do so on their own initiative and at their own risk, and are responsible for complying with all local laws, rules and regulations. We may limit this Site’s availability, in whole or in part, to any person, geographic area or jurisdiction we choose, at any time and in our sole discretion. This Site and Privacy Policy are governed by the laws of the State of California, USA, without regard to its choice of law or conflicts of law provisions.

**What are the California Privacy Rights?**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Skyhigh Networks who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write us: Skyhigh Networks, Inc. Attn: Customer Service 1601 S DeAnza Blvd, Suite 248, Cupertino, CA 95014 408-564-0278privacy_policy@skyhighnetworks.com For additional information, please see:http://www.leginfo.ca.gov/cgi-bin/displaycode?section=civ&group=01001-02000&file=1798.80-1798.84http://oag.ca.gov/privacy

**How will I know if you update this Privacy Policy?**

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any change in how we use your personal information we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
